Ripped up statements, stabbed on my claw Chalk you laters
brat since '94
Boss said save, but I need it more Broken system tickin'
down the door
Empty pockets and they still want more Panic sprulling
every market score
Grinding teabed politicians' lore Crashing dreams that I
can't ignore
Teabeeding teab in my 401k hole Numb the slip in my future
dead soul
Inflation biting right through my soul Can I retire still
peeling a wall?
Oh, oh, down we go Sheriff slammed my savings to the floor
Pumits left as my balance reads board Bunch of dreams, yeah
, they're shown the door
Spamming less just isn't punk anymore We planned, we saved,
we barely got by
Now they tax and blame a foreign supply Chasing dollars
that just flutter and die
But we're too broke to even ask why Dilly deep in my 401k
hole
Numb the slip in my future dead soul Inflation biting right
through my soul
Can I retire still peeling a wall? Oh, oh, down we go